# Nikoloz Palagashvili

+995 514 12 61 61

nikoloz.palagashvili@gmail.com

LinkedIn: <a href="mailto:linkedIn.com/nikoloz">linkedIn.com/nikoloz</a>

#### **OBJECTIVE**

Web Developer, with 2 years of experience, developing high performance websites. I enjoy being challenged and engaging with projects that require me to work outside my comfort and knowledge set. continuing to learn new technologies and development techniques are important to me.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Webiz -FrontEnd Developer

Feb 2020 - Oct 2021

- HRMS
  - Hrms is a Human resources management system.
  - created reusable components
  - built Wizard of employees monthly/yearly expenses analytics and calculations

Technologies: React.js, Redux, Nest.js, Sass, Material UI

- Juno Journey the-juno.com
  - Juno Journey is All in One Platform which has HRIS, Personalized growth plan, Task management, Skills growing and controlling system
  - created search with filters, sorting and highlighting searched word
  - built preview and animations on newly added content
  - created feed with several view types
  - integrated drag and drop, upload
  - integrated functionality of reviews for each unit, managers has ability to ask several type of questions after user finishes unit, and see answers, answers analytics for each unit and also for each user
  - utility functions: traverse recursively over big Json object, transformed from xml file, etc...
  - engagement analytics with chart and time filters
  - virtualized table with sorting and filtering
  - integrated multi-language functionality
  - ability to add/edit/delete/search word from admin panel on 4languages, export words translations with JSON
  - Made tests by Cypress
  - Technologies: React.js, Redux, Sass, Styled Components, react-window, Material UI, React-query, cypress
- JunoBuilder
- JunoBuilder is a website builder, that generates sites with great SEO and responsive design.
- created functionality for admins, to easily fill the website content from json like structure
- built layout arrangement, such as creating, editing, moving, cloning, styling website elements
- took a part in making app responsive
- integrated functionality of video play/pause if user stops screen on video
- integrated functionality of several type effects while scrolling
- Technologies: React.js, Redux, TypeScript, Styled Components,

## Axon - FrontEnd Developer

Oct 2021 - current

- Guidde
  - Integrated upload from Gdrive Technologies: React.js, Redux, Material UI, Gdrive API, Typescript
- Gigz
- Updated Meteor, Meteor packages, Node version and node packages to newest versions
- Changed class based components with their lifecycle methods to functional components with hooks
- Technologies: ReactJs, Context, Typescript, Meteor, MaterialUi

## **EDUCATION**

**Georgian Technical University** *Computer Science* **Bachelor degree**2018 – 2021

## **LANGUAGES**

- Georgian
- English
- Russian
- Hebrew

## **SKILLS**

- Reactjs
- NextJs
- Nestjs
- Expressjs
- Cypress